[
    {
        "front": "ひくい",
        "back": "低い \nlow",
        "chapter": "N4 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "ていか",
        "back": "低下 \nfall",
        "chapter": "N4 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "ていきあつ",
        "back": "低気圧 \nlow pressure",
        "chapter": "N4 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひろい",
        "back": "広い \nwide",
        "chapter": "N4 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "こうだい",
        "back": "広大 \nvast",
        "chapter": "N4 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひろば",
        "back": "広場 \nplaza",
        "chapter": "N4 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "みじかい",
        "back": "短い \nshort",
        "chapter": "N4 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "たんぶん",
        "back": "短文 \nshort essay",
        "chapter": "N4 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "たんじかん",
        "back": "短時間 \nshort time",
        "chapter": "N4 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "よい",
        "back": "良い \ngood",
        "chapter": "N4 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "りょうしん",
        "back": "良心 \ngood heart, good conscience",
        "chapter": "N4 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "わるい",
        "back": "悪い \nbad",
        "chapter": "N4 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "あくにん",
        "back": "あくにん \nbad person",
        "chapter": "N4 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "ただしい",
        "back": "正しい \ncorrect",
        "chapter": "N4 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "せいかい",
        "back": "正解 \ncorrect answer",
        "chapter": "N4 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "せいもん",
        "back": "正門 \nmain gate",
        "chapter": "N4 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "しょうせつ",
        "back": "小説 \nnovel",
        "chapter": "N4 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "しょうがつ",
        "back": "正月 \nnew year",
        "chapter": "N4 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "かわる",
        "back": "変わる \nto change",
        "chapter": "N4 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "たいへん",
        "back": "大変 \nhard, tough",
        "chapter": "N4 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "へんな",
        "back": "変な \nstrange",
        "chapter": "N4 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "へんかする",
        "back": "変化する \nto change",
        "chapter": "N4 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "あかい",
        "back": "赤い \nred",
        "chapter": "N4 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "せきどう",
        "back": "赤道 \nequator",
        "chapter": "N4 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "あかちゃん",
        "back": "赤ちゃん \nsmall baby",
        "chapter": "N4 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "あかしんごう",
        "back": "赤信号 \nred light",
        "chapter": "N4 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "あおい",
        "back": "青い \nblue",
        "chapter": "N4 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "あおぞら",
        "back": "青空 \nblue sky",
        "chapter": "N4 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "せいしゅん",
        "back": "青春 \nyouth",
        "chapter": "N4 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "くろい",
        "back": "黒い \nblack",
        "chapter": "N4 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "あんこく",
        "back": "暗黒 \ndarkness",
        "chapter": "N4 K4"
    },
    {
        "front": "まっくろ",
        "back": "真っ黒 \ndark black / pitch black colour",
        "chapter": "N4 K4"
    }
]